<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Care of Children</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!--    Name Sections-->

    <string name="section1">1. How to find drinking water</string>
    <string name="section2">2. How to find and/or build a shelter</string>
    <string name="section3">3. How to make a fire</string>
    <string name="section4">4. Teach your child to swim</string>
    <string name="section5">5. How to use a knife</string>
    <string name="section6">6. First Aid Basics</string>
    <string name="section7">7. Basic self-defense forever</string>
    <string name="section8">8. Sewing</string>
    <string name="section9">9. Using maps and compasses</string>
    <string name="section10">10. How to get to family, relatives or close friends</string>
    <string name="section11">11. What to do in case of a natural disaster</string>
    <string name="section12">12. Technical maintenance of the vehicle</string>
    <string name="section13">13. Gardening skills</string>
    <string name="section14">14. Climbing trees</string>
    <string name="section15">15. Fishing skills</string>
    <string name="section16">16. Botanical skills</string>
    <string name="section17">17. Teach your child to open canned food with and without a can opener</string>
    <string name="section18">18. Sending an SOS signal </string>
    <string name="section19">19. Using the GPS function in the phone</string>

    <string name="language_rus">Russian</string>
    <string name="language_eng">English</string>

    <string name="double_toast">Please press BACK again to exit</string>

    <!--    Sections info-->
    <string name="info1">Tic-tac-toe, tic-tac-toe.\nTell me two seconds are sick, saints with water, taking the life of a child (Easterner). This is a terrible statistic, but it is flagged over the inoffensiveness of the child. Your child should know how to find water that can be drunk without the risk of poisoning or infection of the patient. If your house does not meet a water pipe, but cheaper water from a well, you are in výgodnom lovenyi. Your aunts can continue to drink water from What the if WSE goodies system gives, and therefore be sure to show you how to take water from this deck, if net electricity. If there is no well in your house, I will come to catch bottled water. Water from a stream or river is not harmless, no matter how clean it is, it was not even in plain sight. You know a kid, they\'ll drink anything as soon as they hunt for a drink, so you really have to hammer it into their heads how you can devalue water. When using the embrace of lazy water, you can lay a lot of diseases on too many, and your child will have to be extremely careful with water. Ha Cay, esli bottled water has finished or ee just failed to show the child how to hone the water, which allows you to use it. It is enough just to boil water in liquid for some time, then to drink it safely. Boiled water can be divided into bottles as soon as it cools down. So be comfortable.</string>
    <string name="info2">Or how easy it is to be warm and cozy even in the wilderness. I think that for a child, water and blood are more important than finding food. Your child should know how to find shelter away from home. Teach him to use branches (preferably with leaves) to build a temporary shelter, in case the child happens to get lost in the forest. You should explain to the child that in the forest can be used as a lining for clothes or an improvised blanket to protect against moisture and cold.</string>
    <string name="info3">There is no need for wisdom — it is important to teach the child the most obvious! Your child should know how easy it is to make a fire. I\'m not even talking about making ugo without matches. Believe me, even making a fire with matches requires a certain skill. This skill needs to be instilled, just like the ability to keep fire under control. You don\'t want to hear on the news that your child set fire to a whole forest.</string>
    <string name="info4">Unfortunately, drowning is the third most common form of accident in children (the first two are burns and falling from a height), so learning to swim is really a vital skill. Swimming is one of the few skills that you cannot unlearn after learning.</string>
    <string name="info5">This is not just survival advice. Every child needs to be shown how to hold and carry a knife for their own safety, even while at home. If a disaster happens, a knife may be the only tool your child will have… the only tool that can help the child survive and hold out until help arrives. Not only can your child use a knife to cut branches for shelter, it can be used for hunting if necessary, or for cleaning caught fish.</string>
    <string name="info6">Even if you don\'t think about disasters, the child should still know the basics of first aid. You need to start learning this with a more conscious outlook. Your child needs to be shown where your first aid items are and how to treat minor cuts and burns. It is also necessary to teach the child to distinguish minor injuries from those that require the intervention of a doctor. If your child is alone at home, the ability to properly treat a cut can save his life.</string>
    <string name="info7">It exactly corresponds to your child that he keeps himself harmless. He necessarily loads something unimportant-he catches the basic techniques quite well. Teach your child to trust his intuition. Esli chelovek say suspicious that rebenku is sure to get rid of the company\'s ego as soon as possible. He must think about what he can take with him, someone must offend, just run away. It is also useful to teach the child how to escape, esli KTO-to find out the Ego. Declare that something that will be written out is twitching away from the attacker, on the contrary, they will definitely twitch in the ego of the parties. This can lead to whoever is attacking the balance chase, and whoever he is invading, he will soon dismiss the child. Also show your child exactly what it is-it holds the ego by the commas, you can escape, be sure to twitch in the fingers of this person. Esli palcý attacking made down from the Zaporozhye of your child, be sure to pull the hand. Fingers are the weakest honor of a loved one\'s traps.</string>
    <string name="info8">Not only will your child be able to use this skill to fix clothes, he will also be able to make blankets or a shelter from small pieces of fabric. And, if the child is not lucky enough to cut himself badly, sewing skills can be used to sew up the wound.</string>
    <string name="info9">Nowadays GPS is installed on every phone, and few people feel the need to use a map. But if trouble happens and suddenly the electricity goes out unexpectedly, your child will need the ability to read a map and use a compass. Not even within the framework of a disaster — your child may someday get lost on a hike. Therefore, it is necessary to teach the child to read the map and find a safe way to people using it.</string>
    <string name="info10">If your child has problems, he needs to know where his family and friends are so that he can find a safe place. It\'s not enough just to know the address, because if your child turns out to be alone due to some kind of cataclysm, there will most likely be problems with communication and electricity, and in such situations GPS is useless. Therefore, it is important to know not only the address of a safe place, but also how to get to it.</string>
    <string name="info11">In both cases, at home and outside the safe walls, your child should know what to do if severe weather is approaching. Schools often practice training alarms to prepare children for tornadoes, fires or earthquakes (depending on the climate and the area where the school is located), but do you do it at home? Does your child know the basics of behavior in situations when he is alone at home, and a real storm is coming to the city? Never expect that at such a moment you will be there and will be able to take care of everything — plan the independent actions of the child. Tell the child that in case of deterioration of the weather (increased wind, severe thunderstorms), he should go to the basement and at the same time stay away from the windows.</string>
    <string name="info12">Of course, it depends on the age. This does not mean that your children should be able to perform an engine overhaul. At a minimum, it is useful to teach a child how to check and top up all the necessary liquids, how to check the oil, how long they can drive between oil changes and how to replace it, how to replace a flat tire, how to replace windshield wipers, etc. These are all simple things that everyone should know. When something very bad happens, it doesn\'t matter if you have a driver\'s license or not. Bce, what matters is whether you can reach your destination alive and well.</string>
    <string name="info13">Teach children how to grow their own food. This skill gives them knowledge and strength Even if you don\'t have enough space for a luxurious garden, growing a vegetable garden with highly productive plants such as strawberries and cherry tomatoes will provide several hours of entertainment. And the knowledge gained during these hours can then save your child\'s life.</string>
    <string name="info14">This skill is just from the category of dangerous, but which you should not forbid the child … at least as long as you can control it. Sooner or later, the child will still try to climb a tree and you\'d better prepare him for it. Teach him to climb a tree and (more importantly) when to stop, realizing that it is dangerous to climb further. In addition to eliminating the potential risk of an accident, this skill can be useful So that your child can hide from predators in a tree or look around and find the right place.</string>
    <string name="info15">Fishing is such a thing that: it is easy to teach, easy to learn and also it does not require particularly expensive tools. I myself went fishing with my father when I was still a child, but despite the fact that I haven\'t practiced this skill since I was 16, I still remember how to use a hook and a fishing rod.</string>
    <string name="info16">Everything is simple here — which local plants can be eaten, and which ones will come down for self-treatment. Since some wild plants are poisonous, it is better to start teaching plants that do not have dangerous counterparts. These are plants such as: nettles, berries (blackberries, raspberries, strawberries), watercress, dandelions, white mar or reeds.</string>
    <string name="info17">There are several tricks in opening preserves that may be useful to your child. One of the safest ways is to rub a metal jar on a cement coating or on the plane of a large stone.</string>
    <string name="info18">Your child should be able to send this signal using the radio or know how it sounds:</string>
    <string name="info19">If it suddenly happens that the child has a phone in his hands, and the GPS works — they need to be able to use it. At least to know how to get home. To make this task easier for the child, you can mark the house on the map in GPS. We know that children get used to new technologies very quickly, so mastering GPS should not be a problem for them. Also, many parents install an application on their smartphone that allows them to track their children by GPS, in case they get lost.</string>

    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="users">Authors</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="rate">Rate us</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>

    <string name="info_kamila"><b>Beknazarova Kamilla Kamoliddinovna</b> (student of 6th grade of specialized school named after Muhammad al-Khwarizmi)</string>
    <string name="info_madina"><b>Madina Abdurashidova</b> (student of 6th grade of specialized school named after Muhammad al-Khwarizmi)</string>
    <string name="info_saida">Mentor: Beknazarova Saida Safibullayevna</string>

</resources>